<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pip.Services Docs – Pip.Services Toolkit for Java</title>
    <link>/toolkit_api/java/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pip.Services Toolkit for Java on Pip.Services Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	  <atom:link href="/toolkit_api/java/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Toolkit_api: How to Get Help</title>
      <link>/toolkit_api/java/get_help/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/toolkit_api/java/get_help/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;Thank you for your interest and for using our products!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our projects are constantly being improved and supported, striving to provide the highest possible quality. We mainly focus on helping developers of complex enterprise systems, as the systems they create are meant to be used for decades. Our goal is to provide stable and long living code, as well as maximize compatibility wherever we can.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If any questions arise while working with our products, or if you would like to share your ideas on how we could improve, please make a post on &lt;a href=&#34;https://stackoverflow.com/questions/tagged/pipservice&#34;&gt;stackoverflow.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you would like to help the project, we recommend checking out the &lt;a href=&#34;../contribute&#34;&gt;&amp;ldquo;How to contribute&amp;rdquo;&lt;/a&gt; section, to familiarize yourself with coding and documentation standards adopted by our team.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;ve found a bug, report it on the GitHub repository&amp;rsquo;s bug tracking page. For any other questions, feel free to send us a &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.pipservices.org/community/contact-us&#34;&gt;message&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Additionally, our team specializes in helping organizations make the switch to microservices and DevOps. If you are interested in such a service, be sure to visit our business &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.entinco.com/&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toolkit_api: Contributing to Pip.Services</title>
      <link>/toolkit_api/java/contribute/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/toolkit_api/java/contribute/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;Pip.Services is a big project that includes a large amount of components, templates, examples, and documentation. This project could never have become a reality without the help of our active community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are always open to new ideas and provide everyone with the opportunity to take part in the project and contribute to it. If you decide to step it up a notch and feel ready to become a part of our team - send us a message! Tell us of your experience and how you would like to participate. One of our team members will be sure to contact you within the next 48 hours.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are multiple ways to help the project:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;report-a-problem&#34;&gt;Report a problem&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before sending an error report, please check to make sure that the error hasn&amp;rsquo;t already been reported, fixed in a newer version, or fixed in the version we are currently working on. If you don&amp;rsquo;t find anything on the problem you&amp;rsquo;ve discovered, go ahead and create a GitHub report in the corresponding repository.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you know how to fix the problem, please include this information in your report. To help our team fix the problem as quickly as possible, include as much information in your report as you can, like: the platform you&amp;rsquo;re using, the versions of any applications/packages/modules you&amp;rsquo;re using, error logs, configurations, etc. If you&amp;rsquo;re not sure how much of the information is relevant, feel free to include everything you&amp;rsquo;ve got.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;improve-documentation&#34;&gt;Improve documentation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As Pip.Services constantly evolves, so do the components that it&amp;rsquo;s made up of. Over time, this can lead to out-of-date documentation. If you have thoughts on how to improve or fix our documentation, don&amp;rsquo;t hesitate to share your ideas with us! You can also contribute by writing-up new documentation, tutorials, and recipes on using the Pip.Services Toolkit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;answer-questions&#34;&gt;Answer questions&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re an experienced user of the Pip.Services Toolkit and you feel that you are ready to give us a hand in answering the questions we get from other developers - we&amp;rsquo;d greatly appreciate your help on the &lt;a href=&#34;https://stackoverflow.com/questions/tagged/pipservice&#34;&gt;stackoverflow.com&lt;/a&gt; forum, or by answering their questions by email.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;expand-an-existing-component-or-write-a-new-one&#34;&gt;Expand an existing component or write a new one&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;ve developed a new component using the Pip.Services Toolkit or expanded one that already exists and would like to share your work - write us, and we&amp;rsquo;ll help you publish your achievements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can also help out in developing new microservices and templates for them, even in programming languages that are not supported by the Pip.Services Toolkit yet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When writing your code, please use our recommendations on &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.pipservices.org/community/codestyle&#34;&gt;formatting code and documentation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;our-appreciation&#34;&gt;Our appreciation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a sign of our appreciation, the most active contributors will be added to our team&amp;rsquo;s page and receive a small prize.&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
